当我还是个实习生 或者第一年受训的医生
When I was an intern, or a first-year doctor in training,
我就知道我的状态出了问题
I knew something was wrong with me.
我时常失眠 郁郁寡欢
I had trouble sleeping, I had difficulty feeling joy,
我会在不合适的时候有哭泣的冲动
I was prone to crying at inopportune times.
更糟糕的是 我难以和病人沟通
Even worse, I had trouble connecting with patients.
我觉得我不能让任何人感到满意
I felt like I couldn't please anyone,
并且容易感觉到绝望和恐慌
and I found myself susceptible to feelings of despair and panic.
我可是个医生 并非自负 我受过很好的训练
I'm a physician! And if I do say so myself, a very well trained one.
即使如此 在实习生支持组和为其工作的社工
Yet it took an intern support group, the social worker that ran it,
我的亲友 以及我的未婚妻（现在的妻子）
close friends and my then fiancee and now wife
共同劝诱之下 我才认识到我需要帮助
to convince me that I might need help.
即使我不承认
Even if I couldn't acknowledge it,
他们能够看出我正受抑郁症折磨
they could see I was suffering from depression.
我不是唯一的受害者 而这正是本期医疗交叉口的主题
I wasn't alone! that's the topic of this week's Healthcare Triage.
在美国医学会杂志上个月发表的研究中
Last month the study in JAMA
研究者审阅了所有关于常驻医师的抑郁和抑郁症状的文献
reviewed all the literature on depression and depressive symptoms in resident physicians.
他们发现了50多个相关的研究
They found more than 50 studies on the subject.
研究表明 大约30%的常驻医师
Research shows that almost 30% of resident physician
经受着抑郁症状的折磨 或者被确诊为抑郁症
suffer from either symptoms, or a diagnosis of depression.
具体的数字及和其他职业的比较是无关紧要的
The numbers and how they compare to other professions are almost beside the point.
医师的职业特殊性使得他们需要长时间照顾他人
Physicians are in a unique position of needing to care for others continuously.
这个负担 加上他们难以帮助自己的事实
That strain coupled with an inability to help themselves,
使医患二者都面对风险
leaves both patients and doctors at risk.
长期研究或那些针对住院医师受训情况的跟踪调查
Longitudinal studies or those that follow residencies over the course of their training,
发现住院医师产生抑郁问题的概率
found that the rate of depressive issues in residents
在一年之内 与开始受训时相比增长了15%
increased more than 15 percent within a year of beginning training.
更糟糕的是 医师所处的职业使得承认自己的健康有问题
Worse, physicians exist in a profession where admitting a problem
会让他们受到比其它职业相比更多的负面影响
carries with it a stigma that's more impactful than in some others.
一个2008年发布的研究调查了密歇根的医师
A study published in 2008 surveyed physicians in Michigan,
询问了他们的工作体验和抑郁症状
asking them about their work experiences as well as their depressive symptoms.
超过11%被评为中到重度的抑郁
More than 11 percent reported moderate to severe depression scores.
他们之中 有四分之一的人
About a quarter of them reported knowing a doctor
听闻有一些医生的职业地位因抑郁症状而受到牵连
whose professional standing had been hurt by being depressed.
患有中到重度抑郁的医生
Physicians with moderate to severe depression
工作效率和工作满意度都因此而下降
had a decrease in work productivity and job satisfaction.
同时他们有大于常人2至3倍的可能表明
They were also two to three times more likely to say
担心 或者确实在心理健康方面难以得到帮助
that they were worried about or had difficulty getting mental health care
在1990通过的美国残疾人法案中
while the Americans with Disabilities Act passed in 1990
禁止了雇主在选择求职者时明确地询问对方的疾病信息
prohibits employers from asking broad questions about illnesses when people apply for jobs,
但是 国家医疗执照委员会仍明确询问申请者的心理健康状态
state medical licensing board still ask specific questions about mental health.
从而造成医师更有可能回避医疗措施
Because of this, physicians are much more likely to avoid treatment.
并且更有可能尝试自我治疗
They're also more likely to self medicate.
有时自我用药可能是合适的 比如抗抑郁物品
Sometimes that medication is potentially appropriate, as with anti-depressants.
但在大多数情况下并非如此
Often it is not.
一个2012年发表在美国医学会外科杂志的研究发现
的A 2012 study in JAMA surgery found that
美国外科医师学会中有超过15%的成员
more than 15% of the members of the American College of Surgeons
在鉴别测试里表现出了对酒精的滥用或依赖
had a score on screening test consistent with alcohol abuse or dependence.
在女性外科医师中 这个概率大于25%
Among female surgeons the prevalence was more than 25%.
患有抑郁症的人滥用或者依赖酒精的倾向比常人更显著
Those who were depressed were significantly more likely to abuse or be dependent on alcohol.
同时 医生比其他人更容易获取药物
doctors have much easier access to drugs than others as well.
因此他们比常人更有可能误用处方药物
Because of this they are more likely to misuse prescription drugs than the general population.
麻醉医生能比一般医生获取更多种类的药物
Anesthesiologist have access to even more drugs than other physicians
因此在他们之中 误用药物的问题更加常见
and their problems are even more common.
在一个2005年的对麻醉医师实训项目的研究中
A 2005 study of anesthesia residency training programs,
发现高达八成的成员曾与工作能力受损的医师共事
found that eighty percent of them reported experiences with impaired residents
20%的人至少听闻一例受训医生因滥用药物而死亡的事件
and almost 20% had experiences with at least one abuse-related death of a doctor in training.
不幸的是 抑郁症和药物滥用可能导致更严重的问题 比如自杀
Unfortunately, depression and substance abuse can lead to further problems including suicide
超过6%的外科医生表明一年之内曾有自杀的想法
more than 6 percent of surgeons report suicidal ideation in the last year
但是其中只有四分之一的人寻求过某种心理治疗的帮助
yet only one-quarter of then sought any kind of mental health treatment.
大多数不寻求帮助的人 害怕如此会使他们难以获得执照
Most who did not fear that doing so would affect their ability to obtain a license,
虽然之前他们还在为轻生的念头而烦恼
even though they were worried about killing themselves.
这个问题在医疗实习生中更为严重
The problem is even worse among medical trainees.
约6%的人表示在半个月之内曾有自杀的想法
About 6 percent of them reported thinking about suicide in the last two weeks.
那些有抑郁病史的人
Those with a history of depression
有大约高于他人四倍的可能产生自杀的想法
were almost four times as likely to report recent suicidal thoughts as those without.
另外 有太多的医生当真把自杀的念头付于行动
Too many doctors act on suicidal impulses as well.
据估计 每年有400名医生结束自己的生命
It's estimated that about 400 physicians commit suicide each year,
这个数字大约是
that's about three times as many doctors
我受教育的宾夕法尼亚大学医学班成员的三倍
as were in my medical school class at the University of Pennsylvania.
综合分析结果发现 男性医师的自杀率
Meta-analysis estimate the rate of suicide among male physicians
大约是常人的140%
is a hundred and forty percent that of the general population.
对女性医师而言这个数字接近230%
Among female physicians it's almost two hundred and thirty percent.
这个问题之所以重要
What makes this important to discuss
并不是因为医生和实习医生中抑郁症的普遍性
is not the prevalence of depression in physicians and trainees,
虽然它明显很严重
although it's clearly too high,
也不是因为医师的自杀率比任何其他职业都高
it's not whether physicians have the highest suicide rate of any profession,
即使有的人认为确实如此
although many people argue that they do.
最为关键的问题是 太多的医疗从业者 尤其是实习生
The critical issue here is that too many physicians, especially trainees,
只是默默忍受痛苦 不敢寻求帮助
suffer in silence, afraid to ask for help
只是因为害怕他们的职业生涯或者个人受到负面影响
for fear that they will be punished professionally if not personally.
我一直对我实习期间的心理问题毫不避讳
I've always been very open about my time in residency,
比如抑郁如何夺取了我生活中的几年时光
and how depression someone robbed me of a few years of my life.
当我回首往事 我认为需要救助别人的长期压力
When I look back, I think the constant pressure to help others
以及时常等着我的无助感
coupled with frequent feelings of helplessness wait on me,
失眠 远离亲友 等原因都使我变得脆弱
a lack of sleep and being away from family and friends left me vulnerable.
眼见与我感情深厚的孩子饱受痛苦 甚至死去
Seeing children I've bonded with and cared for deeply suffer and die
常常使我无法承受
was often more than I could bear.
而且我感到自己生理或是行为的某部分
And I think some part of me whether it be physical or behavioral
有焦虑和抑郁的倾向
is also predisposed to anxiety and depression.
但是我很幸运 感谢那些爱我的人给予我的支持
But I'm lucky, thanks to the support of those who love me
还有两名出色的心理治疗师的帮助 我已不再抑郁
as well as two excellent therapists, I'm no longer depressed.
虽然我一直很小心 提防可能的复发
I remain vigilant, however, against a recurrence.
不管对我还是其他医师 了解自己的心理建康状态都很重要
It's important for me and for all physicians to stay on top of their mental health
而不能坐等危机发生
and not wait for a crisis to act.
幸运的是 我有自己的专业——儿科 也有自己的方向——科研
I've also felt fortunate to be in a specialty - pediatrics, and a focus - research
研究的工作使我不担心病史被发现的后果
where I didn't fear being found out.
当我公开谈及心理治疗 或是我的未来人生规划时
Many colleagues still recoil when I talked openly about therapy,
很多同事仍然不愿讨论此事
or how I plan to go for the rest of my life.
我相信他们依然会觉得这个视频的内容很不合适
I'm sure they'll find this episode concerning as well.
但这是我们不得不讨论的问题
But we can't not talk about this.
有很多医疗工作者还在痛苦之中 如果他们不能获得帮助
Too many of us are suffering and if they can't get help from others,
他们可能在自我帮助的过程中失败
they may try and fail to help themselves.
自杀永远是一个悲剧 而一个医生的自杀则是荒谬的
Suicide is always a tragedy. A physician committing suicide is a travesty.